"1c": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2c": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3c": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4c": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5c": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6c": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7c": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8c": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'

"1c,": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2c,": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3c,": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4c,": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5c,": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6c,": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7c,": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8c,": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'

1cf: 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
2cf: 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
3cf: 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
4cf: 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
5cf: 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
6cf: 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
7cf: 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
8cf: 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'

1cb: 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
2cb: 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
3cb: 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
4cb: 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
5cb: 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
6cb: 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
7cb: 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
8cb: 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'

1cs: 'Screen Print,1-C,Sleeve'
2cs: 'Screen Print,2-C,Sleeve'
3cs: 'Screen Print,3-C,Sleeve'
4cs: 'Screen Print,4-C,Sleeve'
5cs: 'Screen Print,5-C,Sleeve'
6cs: 'Screen Print,6-C,Sleeve'
7cs: 'Screen Print,7-C,Sleeve'
8cs: 'Screen Print,8-C,Sleeve'

1sf: 'Screen Print,1-C,Front Sleeve'
2sf: 'Screen Print,2-C,Front Sleeve'
3sf: 'Screen Print,3-C,Front Sleeve'
4sf: 'Screen Print,4-C,Front Sleeve'
5sf: 'Screen Print,5-C,Front Sleeve'
6sf: 'Screen Print,6-C,Front Sleeve'
7sf: 'Screen Print,7-C,Front Sleeve'
8sf: 'Screen Print,8-C,Front Sleeve'

1sb: 'Screen Print,1-C,Back Sleeve'
2sb: 'Screen Print,2-C,Back Sleeve'
3sb: 'Screen Print,3-C,Back Sleeve'
4sb: 'Screen Print,4-C,Back Sleeve'
5sb: 'Screen Print,5-C,Back Sleeve'
6sb: 'Screen Print,6-C,Back Sleeve'
7sb: 'Screen Print,7-C,Back Sleeve'
8sb: 'Screen Print,8-C,Back Sleeve'

1crs: 'Screen Print,1-C,Right Sleeve'
2crs: 'Screen Print,2-C,Right Sleeve'
3crs: 'Screen Print,3-C,Right Sleeve'
4crs: 'Screen Print,4-C,Right Sleeve'
5crs: 'Screen Print,5-C,Right Sleeve'
6crs: 'Screen Print,6-C,Right Sleeve'
7crs: 'Screen Print,7-C,Right Sleeve'
8crs: 'Screen Print,8-C,Right Sleeve'
9crs: 'Screen Print,9-C,Right Sleeve'

1cls: 'Screen Print,1-C,Left Sleeve'
2cls: 'Screen Print,2-C,Left Sleeve'
3cls: 'Screen Print,3-C,Left Sleeve'
4cls: 'Screen Print,4-C,Left Sleeve'
5cls: 'Screen Print,5-C,Left Sleeve'
6cls: 'Screen Print,6-C,Left Sleeve'
7cls: 'Screen Print,7-C,Left Sleeve'
8cls: 'Screen Print,8-C,Left Sleeve'
9cls: 'Screen Print,9-C,Left Sleeve'

"1 cf": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2 cf": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3 cf": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4 cf": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5 cf": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6 cf": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7 cf": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8 cf": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'

" 1s ": 'Screen Print,1-C,Sleeve'
" 2s ": 'Screen Print,2-C,Sleeve'
" 3s ": 'Screen Print,3-C,Sleeve'
" 4s ": 'Screen Print,4-C,Sleeve'
" 5s ": 'Screen Print,5-C,Sleeve'
" 6s ": 'Screen Print,6-C,Sleeve'
" 7s ": 'Screen Print,7-C,Sleeve'
" 8s ": 'Screen Print,8-C,Sleeve'

"1-cf": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2-cf": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3-cf": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4-cf": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5-cf": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6-cf": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7-cf": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8-cf": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'
"9-cf": 'Screen Print,9-C,Front'

"1c-f": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2c-f": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3c-f": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4c-f": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5c-f": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6c-f": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7c-f": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8c-f": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'
"9c-f": 'Screen Print,9-C,Front'

"1-cb": 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
"2-cb": 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
"3-cb": 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
"4-cb": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"5-cb": 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
"6-cb": 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
"7-cb": 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
"8-cb": 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'
"9-cb": 'Screen Print,9-C,Back'

"1c-b": 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
"2c-b": 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
"3c-b": 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
"4c-b": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"5c-b": 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
"6c-b": 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
"7c-b": 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
"8c-b": 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'
"9c-b": 'Screen Print,9-C,Back'

fcb: 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
fcf: 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'

dtgw: 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
dtgwb: 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Back'
dtgwfb: 
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Back'
dtg: 'Direct To Garment,Front'
dtgb: 'Direct To Garment,Back'
dtgfb:
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Back'

"dtg-nw": 'Direct To Garment,Front'
"dtg-w": 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
"dtg-w b": 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Back'
"dtg-wf/b": 
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Back'

emb: 'Embroidery,n/a,Front'
"emrboidery": 'Embroidery,n/a,Front'
"thread": 'Embroidery,n/a,Front'
"stitching": 'Embroidery,n/a,Front'

"541": 'Direct To Garment,Front'  
"381": 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
"782": 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'

"digital": 'Direct To Garment,Front'
#"garment": 'Direct To Garment,Front'

"dgt-nw f": 'Direct To Garment,Front'
"dgt-nw b": 'Direct To Garment,Back'
"dgt-w f/b":
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
  - 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Back'
"dgt-wf": 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Front'
"dgt-wb": 'Direct To Garment (White Base),Back'

"one color front": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"two color front": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"three color front": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"four color front": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"five color front": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"six color front": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"seven color front": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"eight color front": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'
"nine color front": 'Screen Print,9-C,Front'

"one color back": 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
"two color back": 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
"three color back": 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
"four color back": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"five color back": 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
"six color back": 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
"seven color back": 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
"eight color back": 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'
"nine color back": 'Screen Print,9-C,Back'

"one color sleeve": 'Screen Print,1-C,Sleeve'
"two color sleeve": 'Screen Print,2-C,Sleeve'
"three color sleeve": 'Screen Print,3-C,Sleeve'
"four color sleeve": 'Screen Print,4-C,Sleeve'
"five color sleeve": 'Screen Print,5-C,Sleeve'
"six color sleeve": 'Screen Print,6-C,Sleeve'
"seven color sleeve": 'Screen Print,7-C,Sleeve'
"eight color sleeve": 'Screen Print,8-C,Sleeve'
"nine color sleeve": 'Screen Print,9-C,Sleeve'

"one color print on front": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"two color print on front": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"three color print on front": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"four color print on front": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"five color print on front": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"six color print on front": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"seven color print on front": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"eight color print on front": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'
"nine color print on front": 'Screen Print,9-C,Front'
 
"one color print on back": 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
"two color print on back": 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
"three color print on back": 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
"four color print on back": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"five color print on back": 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
"six color print on back": 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
"seven color print on back": 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
"eight color print on back": 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'
"nine color print on back": 'Screen Print,9-C,Back'

"1 color print on front": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2 color print on front": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3 color print on front": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4 color print on front": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5 color print on front": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6 color print on front": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7 color print on front": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8 color print on front": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'
"9 color print on front": 'Screen Print,9-C,Front'
 
"1 color print on back": 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
"2 color print on back": 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
"3 color print on back": 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
"4 color print on back": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"5 color print on back": 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
"6 color print on back": 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
"7 color print on back": 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
"8 color print on back": 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'
"9 color print on back": 'Screen Print,9-C,Back'

"1-color front": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2-color front": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3-color front": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4-color front": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5-color front": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6-color front": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7-color front": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8-color front": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'

"1-color back": 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
"2-color back": 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
"3-color back": 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
"4-color back": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"5-color back": 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
"6-color back": 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
"7-color back": 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
"8-color back": 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'

"1 color front": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front'
"2 color front": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front'
"3 color front": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front'
"4 color front": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"5 color front": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front'
"6 color front": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front'
"7 color front": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front'
"8 color front": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front'

"1 color back": 'Screen Print,1-C,Back'
"2 color back": 'Screen Print,2-C,Back'
"3 color back": 'Screen Print,3-C,Back'
"4 color back": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"5 color back": 'Screen Print,5-C,Back'
"6 color back": 'Screen Print,6-C,Back'
"7 color back": 'Screen Print,7-C,Back'
"8 color back": 'Screen Print,8-C,Back'
"9 color back": 'Screen Print,9-C,Back'

"1 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,1-C,Sleeve'
"2 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,2-C,Sleeve'
"3 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,3-C,Sleeve'
"4 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,4-C,Sleeve'
"5 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,5-C,Sleeve'
"6 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,6-C,Sleeve'
"7 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,7-C,Sleeve'
"8 color sleeve": 'Screen Print,8-C,Sleeve'

"1-color screen print": 'Screen Print,1-C,Front' 
"2-color screen print": 'Screen Print,2-C,Front' 
"3-color screen print": 'Screen Print,3-C,Front' 
"4-color screen print": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front' 
"5-color screen print": 'Screen Print,5-C,Front' 
"6-color screen print": 'Screen Print,6-C,Front' 
"7-color screen print": 'Screen Print,7-C,Front' 
"8-color screen print": 'Screen Print,8-C,Front' 

"full color print on front": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"full color print on back": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'
"full color front": 'Screen Print,4-C,Front'
"full color back": 'Screen Print,4-C,Back'

"blank": 'No Imprint,nowhere,blank'
"tr-f": 'Transfer,n/a,Front'
"tr-b": 'Transfer,n/a,Back'
